There is something very valid in understanding interest convergence and interest convergence is when you or like your group of people and another group of people that you don't typically align with have a particular alignment in an important space for advancing, you know, the goals of your group.
Right. The thing about interest convergence in this era is that most groups are also deeply intersectional.
And so within that intersectionality, there might be a different relationship to where those interest convergence people are for different people in your group.
Am I making sense? So in the case of a recent podcaster who's now deceased,
there are members of his supporters who also look at Israel with a side eye and feel that they have too much influence in our government.
And that is a very valid point of interest convergence.
Nonetheless, communicating with them is not my ministry.
There is also, some would say, a level of vulnerability to them because of their age group and their ability to still be influenced to shift their points of view to a more humanist POV.
I think it's also important to note that where they're coming from in terms of the ideologies they support impacts individuals in this particular group differently than others.
If I, as a black person in this group, share an interest convergence with them, that is valid.
However, to expect me as a black person whom they have overtly dehumanized, who they have loudly denigrated and who they have committed their time and efforts to removing of all rights.
It shouldn't be expected of me in this group to be a part of aligning them.
And this is also the beauty of community, right?
Because in community, we have different roles and different people have different skills, etc.
I say all that to say that all of you non-black folks in this group that I'm in who want to align with them on interest convergence and do the work of bringing them to where they could be.
I commend you. I support you. I back you.
But I will not be you. And you shouldn't expect me to be.
And I actually don't think you do, but I just wanted to put this on record.
And I'll be you.